<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>House of Peregrine</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/</link><description>Recent content on House of Peregrine</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.houseofperegrine.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Katja Aegerter</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/podcast/katja_aegerter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/podcast/katja_aegerter/</guid><description>Katja Aegerter Katja Aegerter is a Psychologist and Mental Health Professional specializing in the impact of childhood mobility on Mental Health. She has had extensive personal experience and expertise to support globally mobile families and Adult Third Culture Kids. She and her husband share 2 children and have moved to 4 countries together as a family for his assignments with the Swiss diplomatic service.
Her personal experience with moving her family to new countries led her to find that there was very little research on the effect of global mobility on children.</description></item><item><title>Eileen Hausel: Young Expat Services(YES)</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/podcast/yes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/podcast/yes/</guid><description>Eline Hausel is the founder of Young Expat Services or YES. Through Young Expat Services, Eline dedicates herself to helping families from abroad who have established themselves in the Netherlands due to their work. She helps parents find the right school for their child, organizes language lessons and helps with general integration into Dutch culture. She also organizes language and sports camps in the summer for children to work on their Dutch.</description></item><item><title>Alex Ingrim MCSI</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/podcast/alex_ingrid_mcsi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/podcast/alex_ingrid_mcsi/</guid><description>Alex Ingrim MSCI Alex Ingrim is an international financial strategist living in Italy who specializes in financial planning for individuals living abroad. He says that he has an expertise in Americans living in Europe because of the double tax situation that is unique to US Citizens but also individuals from other passport countries are welcome as well.
He has a network of global financial experts and loves to empower people who wish to live more internationally.</description></item><item><title>Stephane Gombauld: Heavnn</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/podcast/heavnn/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/podcast/heavnn/</guid><description>#Finances Stephane Gombauld is a Tax Technologist and Co-founder and CEO of Heavnn- A Global tax optimization technology solution for location-independent people. Heavnn makes life easier and supports the dreams of digital nomads and remote-first companies.
Stephane has an expertise in financial planning for individuals attempting to live independently. This includes strategy, goal planning and execution
His unique ability seems to be having a network of experts as well as a point of view that lends his expertise to the worldview of people who wish to live more internationally.</description></item><item><title>Laser 3.14</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/podcast/laser_3.14/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/podcast/laser_3.14/</guid><description>Street Poet &amp;amp; HOP Genesis Artist
Laser 3.14&amp;rsquo;s name is inseperable from any conversation about Amsterdam and urban art. A unique blend of poet and street artist. Genesis Member Bo Smol of Dutch Web 3 sat down for a rare interview to discuss the history of the artist, the work and the path to creating a poem just for HOP on the streets of Amsterdam that serves as our Genesis NFT.</description></item><item><title>Why Web3?</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/whyweb3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/whyweb3/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s Now. “A more elevated way to create, connect and consume: NFT x House of Peregrine.”
Blockchain technology and NFTS have created new opportunities and models for creating, connecting and transacting. The idea of ownership, community and creator is evolving as quickly as the technology itself.
NFTS, BLOCKCHAIN AND CRYPTOCURRENCY EXPLAINED
WHY INTERNATIONAL LIFE, NFT, AND ART IS A PERFECT MARRIAGE
We have an epic vision at House of Peregrine: to make living internationally more beautiful, connected and sustainable by uniting our existing global community in new and more elevated way.</description></item><item><title>Genesis</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/genesis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/genesis/</guid><description>Could this be an NFT? Laser 3.14’s name is inseparable from any conversation about Amsterdam and urban art. A unique blend of poet and street artist. One day a poem appeared on the street that said: “Could this be an NFT?”; we responded: ”Want to make one together?”
“Bloom where you are planted.” It always hit out of nowhere when I received this as a response. It was 2015 and I was really not coping well with what I saw was a completely bizarre acceptance of normal life in the only place I had called home and wondered if I was the only one seeing it.</description></item><item><title>Genesis Story</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/podcast/genesis_story/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/podcast/genesis_story/</guid><description> Genesis Story The Genesis Members who co-created the Genesis token artwork sat down with Genesis Member Bo Smol of Dutch Web3 to discuss the collab and how it all started with a Poem on the street and making waffles at a W3B 3 Event. In the end it&amp;rsquo;s all about making cool shit with your friends.
Read More</description></item><item><title>Amsterdam</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/amsterdam_first_city/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/amsterdam_first_city/</guid><description> Our Inagural City Amsterdam With its vibe that is grounded in a rich local culture, Amsterdam makes the ideal city begin.
Amsterdam is home to over 100,000 internationals hailing from over 175 different countries. A metropolitan city with a small footprint and a tolerant population we are happy to announce our inagural city will be Amsterdam.
House of Peregrine Concept HOP x Laser 3.14 Local Approach</description></item><item><title>Marketplace</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/marketplace/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/marketplace/</guid><description>Curations and Original Products.
Made by and for the people who have been there.
A Circular Approach to community.
In Your New City. Local and distinctive. From essentials to artifacts. The average person moving to a new city invests a minimum of 10,000 in their new city. This is the first way our marketplace can come in handy. From second hand(coming soon) to just the right thing from a little known artisan you had no idea you needed we have you covered.</description></item><item><title>Memberships</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/memberships/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/memberships/</guid><description>Peregrine Economy Many ways to connect Tokens are minted and serve as memberships. Access to the marketplace of IRL curated products, events and content to start.
Think of it as a POAP of sorts for your years abroad in each city, but with incredible utility.
Genesis
300 (1/1) Laser 3.14
Lifetime Membership
Benefits Include:
Exclusive events Access to curated events Opportunities for collaboration 1/1 Artwork @Laser3.14 Yearly membership worldwide Apply Now Yearly Membership Early Access to content Curated products and services for life abroad Sell on 2nd hand Market (per city) IRL events in your city Ability to contribute to products &amp;amp; content Exclusive artwork per year Continued Utility beyond membership year Join Waitlist B2B</description></item><item><title>My Account</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/my_account/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/my_account/</guid><description>By invitation or nomination Genesis members are mercenaries in their pursuits and want to dive further into web3. Counted among us are artists, venture capitalists, parents &amp; established executives across all industries and nations. 200 memberships @ .25 ETH By application or nomination.
Proof of Attendance Collectables You haven't attended any Events yet.
Event Passes You don't have any event passes right now.
“Now
Is When We Bloom” A mantra for those that</description></item><item><title>Peregrine</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/peregrine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/peregrine/</guid><description>/peregrin/ Having a tendancy to wander: One from abroad. Peregrines exist on nearly every continent of the world yet the name literally means outsider. They are the fastest birds in the world, and adapt to their surroundings so are found as often in cities as in nature. When we were searching for a word to define the essence of who we are as a community it was an immediate fit.</description></item><item><title>Roadmap</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/roadmap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/roadmap/</guid><description>The Future? It&amp;rsquo;s now. “HOP is operating at the bleeding edge of what is possible when Community x Curation x Co-Creation x NFT.”
Connecting the economy of international living with the explosive network effects of NFT is what we are all about. Living internationally is a lifestage and it changes the fabric of social networks, professional outlook and personal lives of those partaking. It&amp;rsquo;s an ideal moment to connect more deeply and meaningfully to oneself and those you are doing life with and a great usecase for web3 tech to invisibly enhance the possibilites.</description></item><item><title>Third Culture</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/third-culture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/third-culture/</guid><description>Third Culture Kids Third Culture Kids have been defined as children who spend a significant amount of their development years(1-18 years) away from their parents’ culture or their passport country. They develop their own internal third culture examining and adopting different aspects of the cultures they are exposed to.
Further, these kids share common characteristics. Among them is they sometimes don’t feel at “home” anywhere but do feel at home with others with the same experience of living internationally.</description></item></channel></rss>