<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>House of Peregrine</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on House of Peregrine</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Apply Now</title><link>/apply_now/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/apply_now/</guid><description/></item><item><title>It's Now.</title><link>/journal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/journal/</guid><description>“Bloom where you are planted.” It always hit out of nowhere when I received this as a response. It was 2015 and I was really not coping well with what I saw was a completely bizarre acceptance of normal life in the only place I had called home and wondered if I was the only one seeing it. I heard it over and over in different forms-a warning to keep my head down and feel grateful for all I have.</description></item><item><title>Membership</title><link>/membership/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/membership/</guid><description>By invitation or nomination Genesis members are mercenaries in their pursuits and want to dive further into web3. Counted among us are artists, venture capitalists, parents &amp; established executives across all industries and nations. 200 memberships @ .25 ETH By application or nomination.
Apply Now Proof of Attendance Collectables You haven't attended any Events yet.
Event Passes You don't have any event passes right now.
“Now
Is When We Bloom” A mantra for those that</description></item><item><title>Roadmap</title><link>/roadmap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/roadmap/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Web3</title><link>/web3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/web3/</guid><description>House of Peregrine Genesis Collectible We have an epic vision at House of Peregrine: to make living internationally more beautiful, connected and sustainable by uniting our global community of internationals in a new way. We believe in producing fewer, high-quality products uniquely curated and designed for and by our members. And we boldly believe that our community will play a critical role in shaping House of Peregrine’s future.
Some call our vision —of building a business by growing a supportive community rather than just another blog or facebook group “too ambitious.</description></item></channel></rss>