<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>House of Peregrine</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/</link><description>Recent content on House of Peregrine</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.houseofperegrine.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Double Dutch</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/podcast/double-dutch/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/podcast/double-dutch/</guid><description>Double Dutch Life living between cultures is different when you’re able to laugh. This is exactly what Derek Mitchell helps us do on lets.double.dutch, his tiktok account that showcases the differences in Dutch, American &amp;amp; British cultures and languages. He’s the boy from Chicago who bought a one way ticket to Amsterdam, seeking a different life and found community and a place to call home . Now as a comedian, writer and actor, most recently appearing in an episode of the popular Apple TV show Ted Lasso, he is living between London and Amsterdam and making us all laugh at the cult in each culture.</description></item><item><title>Alex Ingrim MCSI</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/podcast/alex_ingrid_mcsi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/podcast/alex_ingrid_mcsi/</guid><description>Alex Ingrim MSCI When you live abroad it looks effortless to the outside world. Like you are living a dream. Your insta life can look deceivingly, effortlessly perfect. A dream! We move counties for varying reasons: more travels, a certain kind of lifestyle, or even a plan for the future. Whatever the reason living abroad brings it’s own very specialized financial puzzles and challenges. This is part of the equation that is very rarely talked about but you don’t have to go it alone!</description></item><item><title>Living Abroad</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/podcast/living_abroad/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/podcast/living_abroad/</guid><description>Living Abroad Did you know that Peregrines exist on nearly every continent of the world but the word means “outsider”?
Mickelle Weber, Founder of House of Peregrine opens up about the concept behind House of Peregrine and what is next for the brand and community. Also she shares why she thinks it’s important that we connect IRL, why creating together as adults is so connecting, and how each country you live in creates a new chapter in your life story.</description></item><item><title>Level Up Romance</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/podcast/level_up_romance/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/podcast/level_up_romance/</guid><description>Level Up Romance Moving abroad comes with so much complexity it’s impossible to imagine until you do it yourself. In the height of these moments you are not only navigating through a sea of emotions, but a list of practical matters that need your attention, the realities of daily living and more. Your romantic partnership is in the center of all of the change, stress, excitement and fear that can come up with a move to a new country.</description></item><item><title>Quentin Tarantino</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/events/quentin_tarantino/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/events/quentin_tarantino/</guid><description>Book Signing: Athenaeum Boekhandel Spui “Join fellow HOP members”
Quentin Tarantino x HOP Quentin Tarantino will sign at Athenaeum Boekhandel Spui Amsterdam on Monday 3 April On Monday, April 3 at 4:30 PM, Quentin Tarantino will sign his book at Athenaeum Boekhandel Spui in Amsterdam. During the signing session, only books will be signed, so no posters, merchandise, LPs, etc. No photos or videos are allowed in the bookstore. Tarantino will not speak to the press, not even for a short interview.</description></item><item><title>Why Web3?</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/whyweb3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/whyweb3/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s Now. “A more elevated way to create, connect and consume: NFT x House of Peregrine.”
Blockchain technology and NFTS have created new opportunities and models for creating, connecting and transacting. The idea of ownership, community and creator is evolving as quickly as the technology itself.
NFTS, BLOCKCHAIN AND CRYPTOCURRENCY EXPLAINED
WHY INTERNATIONAL LIFE, NFT, AND ART IS A PERFECT MARRIAGE
We have an epic vision at House of Peregrine: to make living internationally more beautiful, connected and sustainable by uniting our existing global community in new and more elevated way.</description></item><item><title>Genesis</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/genesis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/genesis/</guid><description>Could this be an NFT? Laser 3.14’s name is inseparable from any conversation about Amsterdam and urban art. A unique blend of poet and street artist. One day a poem appeared on the street that said: “Could this be an NFT?”; we responded: ”Want to make one together?”
“Bloom where you are planted.” It always hit out of nowhere when I received this as a response. It was 2015 and I was really not coping well with what I saw was a completely bizarre acceptance of normal life in the only place I had called home and wondered if I was the only one seeing it.</description></item><item><title>Genesis Story</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/podcast/genesis_story/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/podcast/genesis_story/</guid><description> Genesis Story The Genesis Members who co-created the Genesis token artwork sat down with Genesis Member Bo Smol of Dutch Web3 to discuss the collab and how it all started with a Poem on the street and making waffles at a W3B 3 Event. In the end it&amp;rsquo;s all about making cool shit with your friends.
Read More</description></item><item><title>Amsterdam</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/amsterdam_first_city/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/amsterdam_first_city/</guid><description> Our Inagural City Amsterdam With its vibe that is grounded in a rich local culture, Amsterdam makes the ideal city begin.
Amsterdam is home to over 100,000 internationals hailing from over 175 different countries. A metropolitan city with a small footprint and a tolerant population we are happy to announce our inagural city will be Amsterdam.
House of Peregrine Concept HOP x Laser 3.14 Local Approach</description></item><item><title>Casper Faaseen: The Space Between</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/events/casper_fassen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/events/casper_fassen/</guid><description>BILDHALLE x HOP “Personal Invitation to the opening reception for HOP Genesis in the presence of the artist with Unseen Works”
Bildhalle x HOP JCasper Faassen (*1975, NL) grew up in Leiden. It was there that he developed his passion for drawing, painting and art. Famous Leiden masters – Gerrit Dou (1613-1675), Jan Steen (1625-1679) and Rembrandt van Rijn (1606-1669) – were his inspiration. After leaving high school Faassen studied at the University of Amsterdam.</description></item><item><title>Jan Bot: Pablo Nunez Palma</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/events/janbot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/events/janbot/</guid><description>Janbot is dead. Long Live Jan Bot! “The End is Nigh.”
Jan Bot x HOP Jan Bot, made in collaboration with Eye Filmmuseum. Jan Bot Creators &amp;amp; Eye Film Museum Head of Curation will present for the final time.
Free Entrance which is basicly insanity as this is one of the premiere projects in the world in my opinion.
Pablo is one of our own at HOP and had a major hand in the NFT you all hold in your wallet.</description></item><item><title>Marketplace</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/marketplace/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/marketplace/</guid><description>Curations and Original Products.
Made by and for the people who have been there.
A Circular Approach to community.
In Your New City. Local and distinctive. From essentials to artifacts. The average person moving to a new city invests a minimum of 10,000 in their new city. This is the first way our marketplace can come in handy. From second hand(coming soon) to just the right thing from a little known artisan you had no idea you needed we have you covered.</description></item><item><title>Memberships</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/memberships/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/memberships/</guid><description>Peregrine Economy Many ways to connect Tokens are minted and serve as memberships. Access to the marketplace of IRL curated products, events and content to start.
Think of it as a POAP of sorts for your years abroad in each city, but with incredible utility.
Genesis
300 (1/1) Laser 3.14
Lifetime Membership
Benefits Include:
Exclusive events Access to curated events Opportunities for collaboration 1/1 Artwork @Laser3.14 Yearly membership worldwide Apply Now Yearly Membership Early Access to content Curated products and services for life abroad Sell on 2nd hand Market (per city) IRL events in your city Ability to contribute to products &amp;amp; content Exclusive artwork per year Continued Utility beyond membership year Join Waitlist B2B</description></item><item><title>My Account</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/my_account/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/my_account/</guid><description>By invitation or nomination Genesis members are mercenaries in their pursuits and want to dive further into web3. Counted among us are artists, venture capitalists, parents &amp; established executives across all industries and nations. 200 memberships @ .25 ETH By application or nomination.
Proof of Attendance Collectables You haven't attended any Events yet.
Event Passes You don't have any event passes right now.
“Now
Is When We Bloom” A mantra for those that</description></item><item><title>Peregrine</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/peregrine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/peregrine/</guid><description>/peregrin/ Having a tendancy to wander: One from abroad. Peregrines exist on nearly every continent of the world yet the name literally means outsider. They are the fastest birds in the world, and adapt to their surroundings so are found as often in cities as in nature. When we were searching for a word to define the essence of who we are as a community it was an immediate fit.</description></item><item><title>Register Interest: Geneis Wine Tasting Amsterdam</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/events/wine_tasting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/events/wine_tasting/</guid><description>HOP Wine Tasting “We craft our life story with intention. ”
Wine Tasting x Peregrines 50 eu pp Token Holders may bring a +1 We have 2 locations in mind depending on interst levels
Interested? What to expect: A casual night getting to know fellow peregrines in a fantastic setting.
**Special Edition NFT available to those in attendance. Available at event.</description></item><item><title>Roadmap</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/roadmap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/roadmap/</guid><description>The Future? It&amp;rsquo;s now. “HOP is operating at the bleeding edge of what is possible when Community x Curation x Co-Creation x NFT.”
Connecting the economy of international living with the explosive network effects of NFT is what we are all about. Living internationally is a lifestage and it changes the fabric of social networks, professional outlook and personal lives of those partaking. It&amp;rsquo;s an ideal moment to connect more deeply and meaningfully to oneself and those you are doing life with and a great usecase for web3 tech to invisibly enhance the possibilites.</description></item><item><title>Third Culture</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/third-culture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/third-culture/</guid><description>Third Culture Kids Third Culture Kids have been defined as children who spend a significant amount of their development years(1-18 years) away from their parents’ culture or their passport country. They develop their own internal third culture examining and adopting different aspects of the cultures they are exposed to.
Further, these kids share common characteristics. Among them is they sometimes don’t feel at “home” anywhere but do feel at home with others with the same experience of living internationally.</description></item></channel></rss>