<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Journal on House of Peregrine</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/</link><description>Recent content in Journal on House of Peregrine</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Web3?</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/whyweb3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/whyweb3/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s Now. “A more elevated way to create, connect and consume: NFT x House of Peregrine.”
Blockchain technology and NFTS have created new opportunities and models for creating, connecting and transacting. The idea of ownership, community and creator is evolving as quickly as the technology itself.
NFTS, BLOCKCHAIN AND CRYPTOCURRENCY EXPLAINED
WHY INTERNATIONAL LIFE, NFT, AND ART IS A PERFECT MARRIAGE
We have an epic vision at House of Peregrine: to make living internationally more beautiful, connected and sustainable by uniting our existing global community in new and more elevated way.</description></item><item><title>Genesis</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/genesis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/genesis/</guid><description>Could this be an NFT? Laser 3.14’s name is inseparable from any conversation about Amsterdam and urban art. A unique blend of poet and street artist. One day a poem appeared on the street that said: “Could this be an NFT?”; we responded: ”Want to make one together?”
“Bloom where you are planted.” It always hit out of nowhere when I received this as a response. It was 2015 and I was really not coping well with what I saw was a completely bizarre acceptance of normal life in the only place I had called home and wondered if I was the only one seeing it.</description></item><item><title>Amsterdam</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/amsterdam_first_city/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/amsterdam_first_city/</guid><description> Our Inagural City Amsterdam With its vibe that is grounded in a rich local culture, Amsterdam makes the ideal city begin.
Amsterdam is home to over 100,000 internationals hailing from over 175 different countries. A metropolitan city with a small footprint and a tolerant population we are happy to announce our inagural city will be Amsterdam.
House of Peregrine Concept HOP x Laser 3.14 Local Approach</description></item><item><title>Peregrine</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/peregrine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/peregrine/</guid><description>/peregrin/ Having a tendancy to wander: One from abroad. Peregrines exist on nearly every continent of the world yet the name literally means outsider. They are the fastest birds in the world, and adapt to their surroundings so are found as often in cities as in nature. When we were searching for a word to define the essence of who we are as a community it was an immediate fit.</description></item><item><title>Roadmap</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/roadmap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/roadmap/</guid><description>The Future? It&amp;rsquo;s now. “HOP is operating at the bleeding edge of what is possible when Community x Curation x Co-Creation x NFT.”
Connecting the economy of international living with the explosive network effects of NFT is what we are all about. Living internationally is a lifestage and it changes the fabric of social networks, professional outlook and personal lives of those partaking. It&amp;rsquo;s an ideal moment to connect more deeply and meaningfully to oneself and those you are doing life with and a great usecase for web3 tech to invisibly enhance the possibilites.</description></item><item><title>Third Culture</title><link>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/third-culture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.houseofperegrine.com/journal/third-culture/</guid><description>Third Culture Kids Third Culture Kids have been defined as children who spend a significant amount of their development years(1-18 years) away from their parents’ culture or their passport country. They develop their own internal third culture examining and adopting different aspects of the cultures they are exposed to.
Further, these kids share common characteristics. Among them is they sometimes don’t feel at “home” anywhere but do feel at home with others with the same experience of living internationally.</description></item></channel></rss>